{
  "questions": [
    {
      "qid": "p2u2-e1",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "We can’t___________ at the park.",
      "answers": [
        "eat sandwiches",
        "litter",
        "ride bicycle"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "litter"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u2-e2",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "Which of these are not facilities at the park?",
      "answers": [
        "Slide",
        "Swing",
        "Bicycle"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Bicycle"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u2-e3",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "You may get hurt if you _______a tree.",
      "answers": [
        "climb",
        "eat",
        "drink"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "climb"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u2-e4",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "I want to go _________because I want to see the stars and the big moon.",
      "answers": [
        "swimming",
        "camping",
        "dancing"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "camping"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u2-e5",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "We are having a _________party at the country park next week!",
      "answers": [
        "scooter",
        "barbecue",
        "Frisbee"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "barbecue"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u2-e6",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "The man is so disgusting because he ______on the floor.",
      "answers": [
        "runs",
        "flies",
        "spits"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "spits"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u2-e7",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "My mom loves taking ________ of us to create the precious memories.",
      "answers": [
        "photos",
        "strawberries",
        "games"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "photos"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u2-e8",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "Try to catch the ________ when it comes back down!",
      "answers": [
        "Frisbee",
        "kites",
        "drink"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Frisbee"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u2-e9",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "Mom, can you push the _______high for me?",
      "answers": [
        "slide",
        "swing",
        "seesaw"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "swing"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u2-e10",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "Be careful when you are _______ropes! Don’t hit people!",
      "answers": [
        "playing",
        "running",
        "skipping"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "skipping"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u5-e1",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "We take a ________ to cross the ocean.",
      "answers": [
        "bus",
        "ship",
        "plane"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ship"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u5-e2",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "We must _____ ______ and wait for our turn patiently.",
      "answers": [
        "get on",
        "line up",
        "get off"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "line up"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u5-e3",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "We should __________ the bus when we arrive at our stop.",
      "answers": [
        "get on",
        "line up",
        "get off"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "get off"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u5-e4",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "We can take a _____ if we are in a hurry.",
      "answers": [
        "taxi",
        "tram",
        "bus"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "taxi"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u5-e5",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "We take a ________ to cross the sky.",
      "answers": [
        "bus",
        "ship",
        "plane"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "plane"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u5-e6",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "We can't stand in a ______ if there are no empty seats.",
      "answers": [
        "MTR",
        "minibus",
        "bus"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "minibus"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u5-e7",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "We can walk to a place nearby ________ for some exercise.",
      "answers": [
        "on foot",
        "by plane",
        "by helicopter"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "on foot"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u5-e8",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "_________ can only carry one person at a time.",
      "answers": [
        "Ferry",
        "Plane",
        "Motorbike"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Motorbike"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u5-e9",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "We should not take the _____ if we don't have much time.",
      "answers": [
        "taxi",
        "tram",
        "bus"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "tram"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u5-e10",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "We can also take a _______ from Hong Kong to Macau.",
      "answers": [
        "helicopter",
        "plane",
        "train"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "helicopter"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b1",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "cap",
        "captain",
        "chaplain",
        "capital"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "captain"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b2",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "eagle",
        "lizard",
        "dragon",
        "eel"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "dragon"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b3",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "elf",
        "genie",
        "elk",
        "hunter"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "elf"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b4",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "fairy",
        "fairly",
        "angel",
        "dwarf"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "fairy"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b5",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "wrestler",
        "genius",
        "lamp",
        "genie"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "genie"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b6",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "god",
        "king",
        "queen",
        "kin"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "king"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b7",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "monster",
        "mobster",
        "monstar",
        "munchkin"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "monster"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b8",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "sailor",
        "pilot",
        "pirate",
        "private"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "pirate"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b9",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "prick",
        "pincer",
        "princess",
        "prince"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "prince"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b10",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "maid",
        "prince",
        "princess",
        "pony"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "princess"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b11",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "queen",
        "king",
        "quiz",
        "emperor"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "queen"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b12",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "valley",
        "villain",
        "villager",
        "village"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "villain"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b13",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "which",
        "wick",
        "sorcerer",
        "witch"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "witch"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b14",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "wizen",
        "wizard",
        "sorceress",
        "whiz"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "wizard"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b15",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "ghost",
        "angel",
        "zombie",
        "shadow"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ghost"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b16",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "rook",
        "bishop",
        "knight",
        "night"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "knight"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b17",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "dwarf",
        "dwell",
        "hobbit",
        "giant"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "dwarf"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b18",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "dwarf",
        "djinn",
        "giant",
        "huge"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "djinn"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b19",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "murmur",
        "manatee",
        "mermaid",
        "fish person"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "mermaid"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b20",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "allen",
        "alien",
        "anyone",
        "spaceman"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "alien"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b1",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "cap",
        "captain",
        "chaplain",
        "capital"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "captain"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b2",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "eagle",
        "lizard",
        "dragon",
        "eel"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "dragon"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b3",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "elf",
        "genie",
        "elk",
        "hunter"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "elf"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b4",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "fairy",
        "fairly",
        "angel",
        "dwarf"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "fairy"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b5",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "wrestler",
        "genius",
        "lamp",
        "genie"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "genie"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b6",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "god",
        "king",
        "queen",
        "kin"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "king"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b7",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "monster",
        "mobster",
        "monstar",
        "munchkin"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "monster"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b8",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "sailor",
        "pilot",
        "pirate",
        "private"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "pirate"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b9",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "prick",
        "pincer",
        "princess",
        "prince"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "prince"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b10",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "maid",
        "prince",
        "princess",
        "pony"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "princess"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b11",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "queen",
        "king",
        "quiz",
        "emperor"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "queen"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b12",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "valley",
        "villain",
        "villager",
        "village"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "villain"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b13",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "which",
        "wick",
        "sorcerer",
        "witch"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "witch"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b14",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "wizen",
        "wizard",
        "sorceress",
        "whiz"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "wizard"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b15",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "ghost",
        "angel",
        "zombie",
        "shadow"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ghost"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b16",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "rook",
        "bishop",
        "knight",
        "night"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "knight"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b17",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "dwarf",
        "dwell",
        "hobbit",
        "giant"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "dwarf"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b18",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "dwarf",
        "djinn",
        "giant",
        "huge"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "djinn"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b19",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "murmur",
        "manatee",
        "mermaid",
        "fish person"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "mermaid"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu2-b20",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "answers": [
        "allen",
        "alien",
        "anyone",
        "spaceman"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "alien"
    }
  ]

}